<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Gym Fitness</string>
    <string name="action_settings">About</string>
    <string name="nombre_qr">READING QR</string>
    <string name="nombre_ejercicios">EXERCISES</string>
    <string name="nombre_ubicacion">LOCATION</string>
    <string name="nombre_menu">Home</string>
    <string name="nombre_mEjercicios">Exercises</string>
    <string name="nombre_mUbicacion">Location Gyms</string>
    <string name="nombre_mAcercaDe">About</string>
    <string name="nombre_salir">Exit</string>
    <string name="nombre_escanear">Scan</string>
    <string name="nombre_espalda">Back</string>
    <string name="nombre_pecho">Pectoral</string>
    <string name="nombre_hombro">Shoulder</string>
    <string name="nombre_espalda1">REMOVAL IN LOWER PULLEY</string>
    <string name="nombre_espalda2">DEAD WEIGHT</string>
    <string name="nombre_espalda3">REMO WITH BAR</string>
    <string name="nombre_espalda4">"REMO A MANCUERNA "</string>
    <string name="info_espalda1">BACK</string>
    <string name="descripcion_espalda1">This exercise trains the muscles of the back and especially the middle of the back and lattissimus.</string>
    <string name="descripcion_espalda2">The deadlift is one of the heaviest and most intense bodybuilding exercises that stimulates the production of testosterone. At the same time this is one of the most dangerous exercises for the back and knees</string>
    <string name="descripcion_espalda3">This is an exercise for the back in which you align the trunk horizontally and pull the bar upwards. Rowing is the opposite of the bench press, and if you want to develop your upper body well, this exercise should be part of your training routine.</string>
    <string name="descripcion_espalda4">This is a back exercise, which is emphasized in the latissimum and only trains one side at a time. The animation above shows you how to do the technique with the left hand.</string>
    <string name="consejo_espalda1">The rows of sitting cables are good for volume. On the other hand, the wide and wide-grip pulls cause the muscles of the back to widen.</string>
    <string name="nombre_pecho1">BANKING PRESS</string>
    <string name="nombre_pecho2">PRESS INCLINED WITH BAR</string>
    <string name="nombre_pecho3">PRESS OF BANKING WITH MANCUERNAS</string>
    <string name="nombre_pecho4">OPENING WITH HANDLES</string>
    <string name="info_pecho1">PECTORAL</string>
    <string name="descripcion_pecho1">The bench press is an exercise with weights that focuses on the chest muscles (Pectorals). This instruction is for the bar bench press on a flat bench.</string>
    <string name="descripcion_pecho2">A slanted bar press is a variation of barbell bench press and trains the top of the pectorals. The more you adjust the back tilt, the more you train your shoulders and the upper part of the chest muscles.</string>
    <string name="descripcion_pecho3">The dumbbell bench press is a free weight exercise that trains the chest muscles (pectorals) is similar to the bar bench press.</string>
    <string name="descripcion_pecho4">All you need is a flat bench and 2 dumbbells. This exercise trains the chest muscles and is usually done after the bench press.</string>
    <string name="consejo_pecho1">Start chest training with bench press. Stretch between series. Butterflies or openings with dumbbells on a flat bench are usually done after the bench press.</string>
    <string name="consejo_pecho2">Move slowly and concentrate. A training partner can help you lift the bar up when you can not, but it is better if you try to do it alone.</string>
    <string name="consejo_pecho3">I recommend you do 3 sets of 8 to 12 repetitions. Stretch your shoulders and chest muscles between sets and exercises. Inhale through the nose and exhale through the mouth.</string>
    <string name="consejo_pecho4">Do 10 and 15 repetitions. Dumbbell openings are not done with a lot of weight and low repetitions (low repetitions = few repetitions). Perform dumbbell openings on a flat bench after the flat bench bench press and inclined openings after the incline bench press.</string>
    <string name="nombre_hombro1">PRESS MILITAR SENTADO</string>
    <string name="nombre_hombro2">PRESS MILITARY STOPPED</string>
    <string name="nombre_hombro3">FRONT LIFT WITH MANCUERNA</string>
    <string name="nombre_hombro4">FRONTAL ELEVATIONS WITH DISC</string>
    <string name="info_hombro1">SHOULDER</string>
    <string name="descripcion_hombro1">The seated military press is one of the heaviest exercises for shoulder muscles and should be performed at the beginning of training. This exercise is essential to strengthen the shoulders.</string>
    <string name="descripcion_hombro2">The military press is one of the heaviest exercises for shoulder muscles and you should do it at the beginning of your workout. This exercises is essential to strengthen the muscles of the shoulders.</string>
    <string name="descripcion_hombro3">The front elevation with dumbbells, is an exercise for the muscles of the shoulders, where alternate the lifts with each hand.</string>
    <string name="descripcion_hombro4">This is an exercise for the shoulder muscles that trains the front part of your deltoids.</string>
    <string name="consejo_hombro1">Warm up the muscles of your shoulders, before performing a military press. Do not start with a lot of weight. Recommendation for supersets: Military Press with Bar + Lateral Elevations with Dumbbells.</string>
    <string name="consejo_hombro2">Warm enough. (Do not start with a lot of weight). Move slowly and concentrate.</string>
    <string name="consejo_hombro3">There are two variations for this exercise: One, where we wait for both dumbbells to be at the level of the hip and then raise the other dumbbell. And the variation 2, where a dumbbell is raised and the other one is lowered at the same time (in neither of the two, the muscles of the shoulders must rest). Stand in front of a mirror.</string>
    <string name="consejo_hombro4">If you do not use a heavy disk, you can do the shoulder lifts, fully extending the arms. It does not matter if you stand with your left leg in front of your right leg or in the back. If you have hip problems, I recommend that you stand with your legs parallel.</string>
    <string name="consejo_espalda2">The deadlift should always be done first before other exercises. Move slowly and concentrate. Do not lift much weight if you have back problems.</string>
    <string name="consejo_espalda3">Never round your trunk. The most popular back exercises are rowing with barbell, pull-ups and deadlifts. Avoid this exercise if you have back problems.</string>
    <string name="consejo_espalda4">Keep your shoulders still, Do not shrink them at the lowest point of the movement. Stretch your back muscles between sets and exercises. Barbell rowing is similar to this exercise and trains the same muscles.</string>
    <string name="nombre_descripcion">Description</string>
    <string name="nombre_consejo">advice</string>
    <string name="nombre_version">Version 1.0</string>
    <string name="nombre_desarrolladores">DEVELOPERS</string>
    <string name="nombre">Name</string>
    <string name="nombre_correo">Mail</string>
</resources>